SOLD OUT ON YOU
HIT HOMESHOPPING
-How many times do I have to tell you?
-Sorry, ma'am.
-The product is so good!
-Of course!
Dam Ye-jin's a good seller,
so tell them to get her!
They said to change them all to big ones.
Coming through.
We're up next after Dam Ye-jin, right?
Yes, you're up next.
Hello, ma'am.
-Sir, you have to check this.
-Go do your thing.
-Thank you.
-Zoom in.
Okay.
We're done preparing the samples.
Hello.
-Hey.
-Yes?
Is it always a mess like this in studio?
Sorry about that, sir.
Go.
I'm sorry.
It's a complete disaster on set.
Wait, we're about to go live,
but where on earth is Ye-jin?
Dam Ye-jin's not picking up.
What?
What did you just say, Ms. Eom?
We may have to go on without her.
How can we go live without the main host?
I don't know! What do we do?
All right, everyone.
The product I'll be introducing today
is none other than
all-purpose gloves for cleaning!
Don't they look as adorable as I do?
Woof, woof!
They're 100% made in Korea.
Zero synthetic fibers!
Perfect for removing stains!
They're powerful!
Ms. Eom, let's just roll
a recorded segment right now.
If something goes wrong on air,
we'll all be done for.
And that's why…
Sir, we'll go straight into the demo.
We're not getting many calls,
so how about starting the demo right away?
Now, I'll demonstrate
the power of these all-purpose gloves.
Dust!
Oh, my God! Jesus!
Now, let's try removing grease!
All right!
All right! Okay! Like this!
Okay!
Of course, it's hard
to get rid of grease easily.
You, the floor manager. Come here.
All right!
Hey, why isn't this coming off?
You're supposed to wet it first.
All right, our final attack! Hey, grease!
Take this!
Hey, are you okay?
These all-purpose gloves
may not be that effective,
but aren't they charming?
We're losing all the calls!
Please do something, Mr. Hwang!
Well, let's calm down first.
"Calm down"?
Does it look like I can calm down?
I put my faith in Ms. Dam
and had everyone work overtime
for an entire month
to pull together
every bit of stock we could!
Enough. If today's show flops,
I'm filing a lawsuit right away.
Ma'am, there's a big problem!
Our sales are a bigger problem. Look.
LIVE ORDER STATUS
Mr. Hwang, you go in
and do the demo instead.
Tell our host to just talk
and not do anything else.
What? Me?
What?
You can't do it? I guess he can't do it.
Then, what do we do? I'll go. I can do it.
Just make quick cuts
and flash the "Almost Sold Out" captions.
And we'll all take a trip
to the Standards Commission.
Move!
Let go of me!
Let me get on air before they fire me!
All right, I'll get on standby!
For crying out loud!
Who is it? Whose phone is ringing
when we're live…
Hello?
Okay, stand by.
Action.
Everyone, were you looking for me?
I'm greeting you
from a special location today.
I'm your home shopping host, Dam Ye-jin.
Can you guess where I am?
I'm at the highest building in Korea,
the Lux Tower.
Lux Tower!
-She's finally here.
-Yeah!
Why am I here?
Everyone.
-What?
-Look here.
-See this window?
-This is incredible.
This is a year's worth of built-up grime!
It's crazy, right?
Ordinary cleaning products
won't be able to remove this.
All right. Watch this.
I'll spray this cleaner.
All right.
Everyone, do you see this?
I'm wiping pretty hard,
but look at how this grime is still there.
But now,
I'll show you the power
of these all-purpose gloves.
All I did was soak these in water,
and I wrung them out.
You might wonder, "Did she spray them
with bleach or cleaner?"
How nice and damp.
Did you see? There's only water on it.
Now, look carefully.
Where did it all go?
Everyone, you really have to
try this out for yourself.
I'm sure you all know what this is.
Since it lasts even through greasy meals,
they call it "paint lipstick."
DAM YE-JIN
Hey, what are you doing?
Everyone, if I can't erase this,
I'm going to get in big trouble.
-Will these all-purpose gloves save me?
-Geez, this was expensive!
Just wait and watch.
All right.
What do you think?
It's spotless, isn't it?
That is amazing.
Everyone, with these all-purpose gloves,
I just got acknowledged
by a professional building cleaner
with 30 years of experience.
These gloves will instantly make you
a professional cleaner!
You'll get a 10% discount
only during this broadcast,
so place your order now
through our mobile app.
If I had these, I'd be in the majors.
Hey, they're not those kinds of gloves!
Yes, the all-purpose gloves?
They grab every bit
of dust and grime there is.
Even fine dust you can't see
is all trapped right in here.
And it's waterproof inside,
so your hands will stay perfectly dry.
They're also really easy to clean.
A large size?
If you were worried about getting
your hands wet or dirty while cleaning,
you don't have to worry about that now.
Do you see how nice and dry my hands are?
Now,
let me highlight the key features
of these all-purpose gloves once more.
Yeah, didn't I tell you?
You can put your faith in Dam Ye-jin.
Dam Ye-jin really knew what she was doing.
All right, the second set
is almost sold out as well.
We're probably going to end early.
Make sure the next one's ready.
Everyone, this is going
to be sold out within one minute.
So hurry.
I'll throw it back to the studio now.
This has been your host, Dam Ye-jin.
Thank you!
Cut!
I thought I was going to die earlier!
Wait. Hold on.
-Hang on. Let me see.
-What is it?
Just a moment.
Please…
We're completely
sold out of today's stock!
Sold out!
Everyone, they said we're sold out!
Sold out?
Sir!
Sold out!
-Great job!
-We're sold out!
Sir!
-Sold out!
Sold out!
We're sold out!
Sold out! Thank you!
Thank you!
SOLD OUT ON YOU
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
Mechoori, thank you!
Sorry?
Thanks for taking Changsik on a walk.
I didn't. He just followed me.
CHANGSIK
HE DOESN'T BITE
-And that mutt--
-His name's Changsik.
Yes, Changsik.
He needs to be put on a leash.
He'll grow big enough
to high-five you soon.
What? What's that?
Well…
It's like patty-cake…
Anyway,
it's dangerous to let him
follow anyone around.
Come on. What do you mean "anyone"?
Changsik only likes you, Mechoori.
-He does.
-Whenever he sees you,
he follows you around!
-And he follows and follows!
I'm not Mechoori.
What?
It's Matthew Lee.
Right. Matthew…
-Mechoori!
Hey, Mechoori.
Take these and steam them.
It's fine. I have a lot of food at home.
Fine, I'll throw them away.
Okay, fine.
You're going to eat them?
This is too much.
Do you have some for yourself?
Of course. I have tons left.
All right. Just this once then.
Mechoori!
-Hey, Mechoori!
-Hey. Mechoori!
Mechoori…
NO DATA AVAILABLE
NO INPUT SIGNAL
See? It's not working.
The Wi-Fi must be disconnected.
Why is it so bad?
Then call your service provider.
I'll be already dead
by the time they arrive.
-They'll arrive before that.
-What?
Mechoori, where are you going?
Mechoori! Hey!
Come and sit down.
Sit down, everyone.
-Song Ga-in! Song Ga-in!
Have a seat.
Are you here to see Song Ga-in too?
Come and sit down.
Geez.
Is it working?
Go look.
No!
Move it to the right.
Just a bit more.
What about now?
BEST TROT SINGER
SONG GA-IN
Just a bit more!
Just a little more.
And now?
It's working!
It's working now!
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE SENIOR CENTER OPENING
Good job!
-This is awesome!
-It's working really well!
It looks nice and clear.
Gosh, thank you so much.
You can head back now.
Leave it. I'll put that away.
It's fine. And one more thing.
That's the last time
I'm going up on the roof.
Here…
I'm off.
-Mechoori!
He's good at driving too.
Look at him.
He's so prickly.
He never says yes with a smile.
That young brat.
Hey, you old brat!
Even if he speaks curtly,
he's been helping us with everything.
You shouldn't treat him like that.
-He's right!
-Yeah!
ONE DAY
AT JONG-IL'S COW SHED
One, two, three, pull!
Pull!
Okay. One, two, three, pull!
-The teeth look fine.
-That's a relief.
UNERUPTED TEETH
STILL COVERED BY GUMS
That was exhausting, wasn't it?
Mechoori's better than you
at pulling calves now.
Hey, don't be stupid.
Don't you know how many calves
I pulled at your shed?
You don't need to deliver them anymore.
Mechoori's really come into his own
handling them now!
Geez, do you know why I'm asking
Mechoori to pull your calves?
I pity the calves that will have to see
that ugly face of yours their whole lives.
I wanted to let them
see Mechoori's handsome face for a moment.
Are you done talking?
Nope, not at all.
Have you forgotten
when you used to get beaten up
all the time?
Bring it on then. How about a bull fight?
Go ahead.
This is my last time
helping you out in the shed.
-I'm off.
-Thanks.
Wait, there's one more!
Come on! Hurry!
Come here.
Damn it.
That's not all.
He even chopped all your firewood for you.
ON ANOTHER DAY,
HOUSE CALL FOR FIREWOOD CHOPPING
Geez!
Please…
He's right!
And you remember that other time?
AND ON ANOTHER DAY,
VILLAGE HALL BEEHIVE REMOVAL
Grab the end. It's okay.
-Find your balance.
-Don't be scared.
DEOKPUNG COMMUNITY CENTER
Yeah, you're right.
That's right! That day was really fun too.
AND ON YET ANOTHER DAY,
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE'S KIMCHI-MAKING DAY
Mechoori, open up.
"It's Matthew Lee, not Mechoori."
And there's that.
Why aren't you mentioning that?
You know. That.
TYPHOON ROMEO HITS DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
Oh, come on.
Damn it.
And you still think he's prickly?
I do remember something else.
Our village might fly away at this rate!
This is insane.
Come on. Let's close the window.
-Close it.
-It's not closing.
TYPHOON JULIET HITS DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
Come on!
Right!
We would've been in huge trouble
if it weren't for him.
-But he wasn't like this from the start.
-Yeah.
He's finally become a bit nice.
What did I tell you?
Mechoori's like streusel bread.
Rough on the outside
but soft on the inside.
Streusel bread!
You're right. Should I go buy
some streusel bread?
-Sounds nice.
-How many? Two?
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE BUS STOP
Mechoori, stop!
I'm going to get off here!
Thanks.
When are you heading back?
I'm not the village bus driver.
I'm heading back around 4:30 p.m.
You can wait for me then or whatever.
I said 4:30 p.m., okay?
Okay, 4:30 p.m. See you later.
Bye.
A simultaneous live broadcast?
You know how Dam Ye-jin is.
Once she's set on something,
she stops at nothing.
My heart was racing,
and I was nervous and anxious all morning.
I'm filing a workers' comp claim!
You have to add my name as well.
The partner company people
threatened to sue me!
-I really--
-Okay, I get it! You did great.
Hey, it all ended well today.
You know how intense Dam Ye-jin is.
But what's with her anyway?
I know she's popular,
but she's filming commercials…
WHETHER IT'S RAIN OR SNOW
IONA
She's a brand ambassador,
and she's even appearing on Running Man.
What is she even doing on there?
What is she going to do? What?
Superstar Dam! Gosh, no need to be sorry!
No, it was good!
Gosh, a true professional
would never complain about that…
Lunch?
I'll come by myself.
Hurry? Okay, I'm coming.
Are you all right?
Weren't you even scared?
Gosh, I'm more afraid of leftover stock.
I'm late for an engagement,
so I'll get going.
Ye-jin!
-Hello.
-Could we have an autograph?
-Thank you.
I loved the show.
I'm a huge fan.
Could I get a photo with you?
-Thank you.
I'm a huge fan.
Here's your dish.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
Lucky you. You always arrive
right when the food comes.
I'm sorry.
But I practically
flew over here to see you.
Eat up.
Let's watch a movie later.
We can go after we eat.
You said you wanted to see this.
I'm sorry.
Our new program's launching tomorrow,
so I have to head back
to work after dinner…
You know how many surgeries I do each day?
I'm probably
one of the busiest people in Korea.
But "busy" is something…
What's with this knife? It's light.
It cuts well. And it's cute.
This would be nice for a fancy meal.
Yeah, this is perfect.
-Are you listening to me?
-You pass.
I'm sure our customers would love this.
Should I try to sell it?
Let's break up.
Ui-seok, are you angry?
I'll postpone the meeting.
Let's go see the movie.
Forget it. You're just going
to keep stepping out to take calls.
No,
I'll really--
Do you really think this is
about me waiting a few minutes?
What's the matter?
Aside from surgeries,
I see about 300 outpatients a day too.
But do you know why
I still make time to date?
Because I have a personal life.
I want to live like a human being.
I just want to laugh
and enjoy my time with you.
But with you, Dam Ye-jin.
Not home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
But…
I can't separate
those two that distinctly.
Then, you can just date that job of yours
that you love so much.
The gentleman already paid.
Actually, it's not because of that.
Your cutlery…
Could I know who you bought these from?
Hey, Mr. Hwang.
Ms. Dam!
You almost made me faint earlier!
I… Oh, my gosh!
Mr. Hwang, I found our next product.
This is cutlery made
from premium stainless steel
and Nordic wood.
Both its features
and performance are amazing.
Let's test it and get in touch
to make it our next product.
Hang on.
A Nordic walnut handle
that's been oiled twice
and intricately carved
to a 1.5mm thickness…
I can just tell how well it'll cut.
Let's do it!
-All right!
Okay. All right, then.
I'll wait in the lobby.
Don't be late.
JI YUN-JI
HIT'S TOP SELLER FOR 2024
DAM YE-JIN
HIT'S SECOND TOP SELLER FOR 2024
This business
is pretty cruel,
don't you think?
Sales aren't everything.
But they use photo size
to show the difference.
I heard you almost made a scene again.
I actually did.
We sold 230% of our target.
That's a huge scene.
But you're a pro in that area.
I bring in more with one jar of cream
than you do with ten rags.
Right.
While you sell one, I sell ten.
What?
Isn't it a relief
that I don't sell cosmetics?
Look here, Dam Ye-jin.
Hey.
We have plans.
See you later.
What's the deal with Ji Yun-ji?
Geez, she's evil to the bone.
She insults you
instead of being a supportive senior.
Are you being upset on my behalf?
Damn it, I've been upset all day!
If you do that to me again
on a live broadcast,
regardless of our four-year friendship,
I'm gone. Got that?
I got it, so you can stop.
You don't yell at a woman
who just broke up.
Why did you get dumped?
I never said I got dumped.
I mean…
-You're so busy.
-So what?
Everyone's busy.
But not everyone lives like you.
How do other people live then?
You know,
I work to eat chicken and beer
after clocking out.
I smile when I think
about chicken and beer,
and I can endure any crap
that people give me.
That's what helps me breathe.
Everyone has something like that.
A lover, a celebrity they like, a hobby,
or maybe just a restaurant they like.
But you?
You just never clock out of work.
Well, it just happens
that when I'm working--
Exactly. So why are you working?
Don't we all work to live a decent life?
But do you know why
I still make time to date?
Because I have a personal life.
I want to live like a human being.
I just want to laugh
and enjoy my time with you.
But with you, Dam Ye-jin.
Not home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
DOESN'T CUT WELL ENOUGH
PASTEL POPULAR AMONG THE YOUNG
My daughter, Ye-jin. Your health
is the most important thing.
No matter how busy you are,
make sure to eat well.
Hey, I was checking the responses
for the previous Airix product.
And for the new one, I thought…
Okay, I'll check that right now.
Well… Next week…
I don't think I'll be available next week.
How about the week after that,
on the 29th?
I only have one meeting at 3:00 p.m.,
so I can make time in the morning.
POEMS BY PARK JOON
That's hot.
The wavy rubber tip
at the top of the nozzle…
It's suitable for all hair types,
but especially great for straight hair.
TAKE ONLY WHEN UNABLE TO SLEEP
GOJEUNEOK BIO
Do you
really want to see me lose it?
I'm nothing
without you or money.
Are you trying to make me the villain?
-I said I don't need it.
-Just use it, will you?
So I have to just because you tell me to?
I won't.
Just use the new one. It'll be nice
to ride one with a new engine.
I hate loud things.
Tractors are supposed to be loud.
I thought you'd like it.
I swear, you're so difficult…
-If that's it, I'm hanging up.
-Wait.
About that thing…
So you haven't changed your mind?
No. Go ahead as planned.
It's hard covering up
the bags under your eyes today.
Are you tired?
No, I'm at full power right now.
That's Beauty Song's
new product, isn't it?
Yes, I bought it since it was going viral.
It's awesome. Just look.
Your skin looks silky smooth.
It's good.
Sir, is this centered?
-Left? Right? Okay.
-Good.
Can you place that in the center?
Hello.
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
EMPLOYEES ONLY
Hang on.
You smoke, Mr. Hwang?
What is it?
Nervous about your first prime time show?
-Well…
-I understand.
Being a merchandiser is tough.
People say the "MD" in merchandiser
means "must do everything."
And they say if you're an MD at HIT,
it means "You're making me crazy,
Dam Ye-jin."
Spill it! What's the matter?
WEEKLY BROADCAST SCHEDULE
THE JI YUN-JI SHOW
Damn it!
How about changing the background color
to violet like the brand's color?
Violet?
And…
The light might reflect off the products,
so please check the angles.
Ma'am?
Well…
Did you get the studios wrong?
This is the Saturday prime time studio.
I guess you haven't seen
the changed schedule.
Tonight's prime time slot
has changed to The Ji Yun-ji Show.
We're launching Beauty Song's compact.
Beauty Song?
Yeah.
It seems the set hasn't been cleared yet.
Ms. Song.
Ms. Dam didn't see the updated schedule.
Oh, my.
You really haven't changed, Ms. Dam.
Aren't you sick
of saying "I didn't know" as an excuse?
-Everyone, I think we should hurry.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Let's take all these out.
-One, two!
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's proceed.
MAKING ME CRAZY DAM YE-JIN
ANSWER WITHIN TEN SECONDS
Don't answer. It'll be a disaster.
-Should I turn it off?
-No, that would be worse.
She wouldn't go straight
to the director, would she?
Come on. Even if she's practically
a human bulldozer,
she'd be insane to just barge in there.
Right?
I didn't hear you knock.
You're the one who skipped protocol first.
Why was the schedule changed
to The Ji Yun-ji Show?
How could you do this
without even telling me?
At this rate,
we'll be crushed by CT Life Shopping
before the next quarter.
Beauty Song's Song Myeong-hwa Compact
was the one that boosted CT's sales.
So if they're coming to us,
shouldn't we offer
our prime time slot on Saturday?
Why does it have to be my slot?
The prime time slot
is for best-selling products,
not for hosts who have good sales.
You know that beauty products
are the real moneymakers.
Ma'am,
our team's average target achievement rate
for the past three months is over 180%.
And with prime time consumers,
we'll be able to show even better results…
That's right.
It's the brand that both
Haeseong Duty Free and Lux Duty Free
were desperate to get on board
but failed to in the end.
L'Étoile.
We'll need a brand like that
to push out Beauty Song.
I don't sell cosmetics.
That clause has always
been in my contracts.
But I guess you forgot.
I'll find a product
that is as good as L'Étoile's.
The Danish royal tableware
you mentioned before--
You seem mistaken about something.
But L'Étoile is the only brand
that would allow you
to retake the prime time slot.
If you can't do that,
then your dream of hosting a show
with your name on it will end here.
-Ma'am!
-When are you going to stop running away?
Are you going to betray
the partner companies, merchandisers,
and producers relying on you over this?
The next time you enter my office,
you'd better have
a contract with L'Étoile.
Ms. Dam.
Have you lost your mind?
How could you barge in there like that?
So what did the director say?
What is it? What did she say?
She said that if I want my spot back,
I have to bring L'Étoile on board.
-L'Étoile?
-What?
You mean the French brand, L'Étoile?
But Ms. Dam doesn't do cosmetics.
That hurts.
Damn it. How can Ms. Dong be so cruel?
Wait!
How in the world
is she going to bring in L'Étoile?
I know.
It's not like I'm a celebrity or anything.
If word gets out that you're in Korea,
the duty-free retailers
who sent in offers will be all over you.
Then, our confidential information
would be exposed in no time.
Look, no one in Korea would recognize me…
Where are we going?
What's trending in Korea these days?
First, let me take you to your hotel.
You can rest there
until your evening meeting.
You don't mean tonight, do you?
I do, sir.
But I just got here from France.
Well, the meeting
is what you came here for.
Did you say the raw material supplier
was called Gojeuneok Bio?
Yes.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kang Mu-won, CEO of Gojeuneok Bio.
Hello. I'm Eric Seo,
Executive Director at L'Étoile.
Nice to meet you. Please take a seat.
We offered very favorable terms
in the new raw material supply contract.
Have you considered it?
CONTRACT AMENDMENT PROPOSAL
Of course. I considered it very carefully.
Then--
But I won't be able to give
the answer you want.
I'm sorry you had to come all this way.
To be honest,
this is hard to understand.
We increased
the previous order volume by five times,
and we also adjusted the terms to be
much more favorable to Gojeuneok Bio.
You're worried you won't be able to manage
-the increased volume, right?
-Yes.
Yes, I think that seems
to be the biggest concern…
I mean, it is the biggest concern.
Then,
we'll come up with a way
to resolve that issue.
No,
let me be clear about this.
Gojeuneok Bio
will not renew our contract with L'Étoile.
You must be tired.
Should I take you back to the hotel?
Mr. Cha.
There's something strange about Mr. Kang.
It was like he was speaking
for someone else.
Then I'll look into Gojeuneok Bio
a bit more.
My sister must be worried sick
that I'm slacking off here.
Our deputy CEO, Michelle,
is especially worried about you.
Oh, dear. It's raining.
We should get this done quickly
before it's too late.
The first set has sold out.
Oh, my!
It's sold out. My gosh!
It's already sold out.
You know, it's only been 30 minutes
since we started the show.
We have an hour,
but it's already sold out. At this rate…
All right!
Since it's late,
how about a late-night snack--
What? So we can watch her show?
What do we do with our remaining time?
Why isn't this turning off? Damn it!
I am so surprised too.
Just go home now.
Right.
I don't even want to be
in the same building
as Ji Yun-ji right now.
Get up.
What's really surprising is
that blotting paper
doesn't seem to stick to this at all.
-Right.
-If I put a sheet
of blotting paper on my face…
Look. Seriously.
It just falls off right away.
ACTRESS SONG MYEONG-HWA'S
BEAUTY SONG COMPACT
-We demand compensation!
WE SUFFER EVERY DAY
I'm sorry. I apologize.
My skin feels so moist.
I gave away all of my blotting paper
to my friends and acquaintances.
-Really?
-Yes, seriously.
I see.
As time passes by,
we want to make our skin smooth
and gentle.
When you get to your forties,
fifties, and sixties…
Stick with your usual size.
Customer 8782 is asking about washing it.
That's why we prepared
oil directly imported from Italy.
Even if you put it in the washing machine…
I'll discuss it with them right away.
The lineup is made up of these three…
Ms. Dam, you've already hit
the maximum dose and duration.
If you keep overusing sleeping pills,
you may experience serious side effects,
such as sleepwalking, memory loss,
and even respiratory depression.
You could seriously hurt yourself.
Just one pill per day.
Please stick to that.
When are you going to stop running away?
Aren't you sick
of saying "I didn't know" as an excuse?
We'll get ready now!
-Excuse me.
-Don't step on that!
Out of the way!
Please take this out too.
-Passing through.
-Excuse me.
Ms. Dam?
We're starting now. There's no time.
MS. ANGRY EOM
Ms. Eom, is it another
simultaneous live broadcast today?
Why isn't she picking up her phone again?
Is she not here yet?
This won't do.
I'll look for a recorded segment.
You try to do something here.
-Do what?
-Anything.
-Just do something.
-What…
Hey! You little…
-Sorry.
-Geez.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
Sorry, I'll go get ready.
Hang on. Is something wrong?
I'm fine.
For crying out loud.
I'm really okay.
We hope all your days
are healthy days with Binox.
Thank you for all of your love
and support today.
This was your home shopping host,
Dam Ye-jin. Thank you.
Great job!
You can't focus on just the symptoms.
Real issues and relationships
that you can't avoid are connected to it.
There are underlying factors
behind your insomnia.
To break this nightly cycle of insomnia,
you have to resolve the root cause first.
-Goodbye!
-Bye!
It's time to face it now.
You must figure out
what is deep down inside
that's pulling you down.
Hey, don't joke around.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Get home safely.
Mechoori!
-Did you have a good day?
-Yeah.
Thanks.
-What's this?
-Striped maple extract.
I knew you'd never drink it if I told you.
I saw you vomiting.
So don't complain and just drink it.
It helps with stress-related gastritis.
I really can't drink it.
You don't have to bring in L'Étoile
if you don't want to.
What about our team if I don't?
If we get fired, we can just go to CT.
Hey, after spending four years
working with someone
who sells everything besides cosmetics,
I have experience
in every field except makeup.
You could say I'm an all-rounder.
Do you know what this is?
Four years ago, after our first show,
you left this product description
behind in the studio.
I think we reached
only about 30% of our target rate.
Remember how we totally messed up?
I wondered if it was a mistake
working with you,
but the moment I saw that,
I felt relieved.
I knew if you were this dedicated,
I could trust you.
But now,
you sell over 200% of our target rates.
Seriously, aren't you proud?
What are you trying to say?
There are a lot of people
who trust you now.
So you should trust yourself too.
There's still so much left.
That's my sister, right?
No, it isn't.
I'm not sure if you've heard,
but the biggest home shopping company
in Korea is called HIT.
It's been consistently
sending in offers since last year.
I know HIT. They contacted you?
Yes, it's a host named Dam Ye-jin…
Who?
Home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
It seems like HIT found out
that you're in Korea.
-She's asking for a meeting.
-Set it up as soon as possible.
What? But, sir, we still have to deal
with the renewal contract--
Mr. Cha, I've been stuck here
looking at papers for a whole week.
Don't you understand how desperate I am
to just talk to someone?
Don't you?
Hi…
I mean, hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
I like the proposal.
Did you read through it carefully?
Of course. You did too, right?
Our meeting was scheduled in a hurry,
so you could've missed something.
Please take another good look.
I've already reviewed it thoroughly.
We'll review your proposal
with a positive outlook.
I actually didn't expect our meeting
to go so smoothly like this.
I believe HIT has been sending offers
to L'Étoile since last year.
So could I ask the reason for this?
Well, we also have one condition.
So, you're saying
we have to work with you to resolve
your raw material renewal contract?
Yes. If you can help us
resolve this matter,
then I'll prioritize HIT's offer
as soon as I return to France.
Then, I'll take responsibility
and solve this matter.
You're accepting my proposal?
Yes, if you promise
to come on board right now.
I don't have much time either.
Since we don't have much time,
why don't we proceed on two fronts?
You focus on convincing
the CEO of Gojeuneok Bio,
and I'll focus on convincing
the raw material farm owner.
The farm owner? Why?
Gojeuneok Bio cultivates
their own raw materials.
If we get the farm owner on our side,
we'll have a better advantage negotiating.
By the way…
Should we officially exchange numbers now?
Sure.
Here.
Gosh, my feet.
Let's rest a bit.
Oh, my gosh.
Hey, perfect timing.
Hello, Su-min.
Give me a ride to the living room.
Pardon?
-Hey, why are you turning around?
-Pardon?
-Hey!
Hey, Su-min… Hello, Su-min!
-Come here.
-Pardon?
-Hello--
-My name is Su-min.
-Hey, Su-min. Come back here.
-I am not able to do that.
Hey, where are you going?
My name is Su-min.
Fine. Just go.
Pardon?
You're out.
I do not understand.
What am I doing?
-I do not understand what you are saying.
-Be quiet.
L'Étoile.
Let's see.
The key ingredient of the essence
seems to be WF-Mushroom.
Find more data on this.
WF-Mushroom is the key ingredient
in La Fin Essence
and makes up over 90% of the formula.
It's an extract
of the white flower noori mushroom.
Can you explain more
about the white flower noori mushroom?
The white flower noori mushroom
is native to Korea,
and its extract is known
for boosting skin elasticity,
reducing pore size,
and providing antioxidant benefits.
I like the data.
You're useful. You get a pass.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
All done.
You're heading to the farm?
Yes, I wanted to check it myself.
What's the exact address?
We only know
that it's in Deokpung Village.
Then, I'll just go and ask around.
There can't be many farms
that big in the country.
From here, go straight.
GOODBYE
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE EXIT
Oh, no. I can't move over.
Sir, let me pass.
Can you move your vehicle?
What's with him?
Hey! I said move your car!
It seems like you're not from around here.
But here, we have things called rules.
This is a one-way street.
I've come much further in.
I have the right of way.
This is the way out.
Whoever can back up faster should move.
Can't you see this?
Tractors can't reverse.
How can tractors not reverse?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not being ridiculous.
This tractor can't reverse
because it fell into a ditch.
Because it fell into a ditch?
Then, this convertible
can't reverse either
because that's uncool!
SOLD OUT ON YOU
THANKS TO SPECIAL GUEST PARK JI-HWAN
What happened to your ear?
If you keep loitering,
I'll report you for obstructing business.
That tractor!
You're not putting her in charge
of cosmetics again, are you?
I'm Dam Ye-jin. I don't back out
once I've made up my mind.
Darling! Hurry and grab the chickens.
Hey, Changsik!
-Why did you come here?
-I'm here for one thing.
Make an official appointment.
Instead of that, I'll do it my way.
Is this the way you were talking about?
My goodness!
What's your deal?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park